<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resume>
  <name>Homed Rekabdar</name>
  <contact>
    <email>homed.rekabdar@gmail.com</email>
    <phone>(470) 965-1875</phone>
    <github>https://github.com/HomedRe</github>
    <linkedin>https://www.linkedin.com/in/homedrekabdar</linkedin>
  </contact>

  <summary>
    Technical Support Specialist with over 2 years of experience in troubleshooting, 
    client support, and application setup. Pioneered the installation of new software 
    versions and collaborated with the development team to resolve issues during and 
    after deployment. Skilled in SQL for data analysis, issue resolution, and root 
    cause analysis. Successfully closed nearly 2,000 support cases while consistently 
    exceeding performance expectations through top adherence, high call resolution 
    rates, and strong evaluation scores. Seeking to leverage my technical expertise 
    and programming background to contribute effectively as an Application Support Engineer.
  </summary>

  <skills>
    <skill>Support and Troubleshooting: Tier 1 and 2 support, problem-solving, working on unknown/new tasks (adaptability).</skill>
    <skill>Database: SQL, SQL Server (Sybase, MSSQL).</skill>
    <skill>Programming and Web: Basic XML, HTML, CSS, JavaScript; exposure to C, C++, C#, Java.</skill>
    <skill>Documentation: Knowledge base creation, internal resources.</skill>
    <skill>Communication and Teamwork: Mentoring peers, cross-team collaboration.</skill>
  </skills>

  <experience>
    <job>
      <title>Technical Support Specialist - Escalation</title>
      <company>Carestream Dental</company>
      <location>Remote</location>
      <date>June 2023 - Present</date>
      <duties>
        <duty>Resolved nearly 2,000 technical support tickets, ensuring high client satisfaction and fast issue resolution.</duty>
        <duty>Performed root cause analysis and validated critical data with SQL queries to prevent errors and support seamless application performance.</duty>
        <duty>Led deployment of new software versions, collaborating with development teams to prevent post-launch issues.</duty>
        <duty>Mentored peers on advanced workflows, reducing repeat escalations.</duty>
        <duty>Authored knowledge base articles and internal resources, improving team efficiency.</duty>
        <duty>Streamlined and documented WinOMS v9.x (Sybase) to v10.x (MSSQL) migrations and updates.</duty>
      </duties>
    </job>
  </experience>

  <education>
    <degree>Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering</degree>
    <year>2017-2021</year>
  </education>

</resume>
