<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resume>
  <name>Homed Rekabdar</name>
  <contact>
    <email>Homed.Rekabdar97@gmail.com</email>
    <phone>(470) 965-1875</phone>
    <github>https://github.com/HomedRe</github>
    <linkedin>https://www.linkedin.com/in/homedrekabdar</linkedin>
  </contact>

  <summary>
    Technical Support Specialist with over 2 years of experience in troubleshooting, client support, and software deployment. 
    Skilled in SQL, scripting, and data analysis for diagnostics and root cause resolution. Proven track record of collaborating with 
    development teams to implement new software versions and resolve complex issues post-release. Closed nearly 2,000 support cases 
    with top adherence and customer satisfaction scores. Seeking to leverage my technical expertise and programming background to 
    contribute as an Application Support Engineer and progress into an Application Engineer role.
  </summary>

  <skills>
    <skill>Technical Support and Troubleshooting: Tier 1 and 2 support.</skill>
    <skill>Problem-solving, working on unknown/new tasks (adaptability).</skill>
    <skill>Database: SQL, SQL Server (Sybase, MSSQL).</skill>
    <skill>Programming and Web: Basic XML, HTML, CSS, JavaScript; exposure to C, C++, C#, Java.</skill>
    <skill>Documentation: Knowledge base creation, internal resources.</skill>
    <skill>Communication and Teamwork: Mentoring peers, cross-team collaboration.</skill>
  </skills>

  <experience>
    <job>
      <title>Technical Support Specialist - Escalation</title>
      <company>Carestream Dental</company>
      <location>Remote</location>
      <date>June 2023 - Present</date>
      <duties>
        <duty>Resolved nearly 2,000 technical support tickets, ensuring high client satisfaction and fast issue resolution.</duty>
        <duty>Performed root cause analysis and validated critical data with SQL queries to prevent errors and support seamless application performance.</duty>
        <duty>Led deployment of new software versions, collaborating with development teams to prevent post-launch issues.</duty>
        <duty>Mentored peers on advanced workflows, reducing repeat escalations.</duty>
        <duty>Authored knowledge base articles and internal resources, improving team efficiency.</duty>
        <duty>Streamlined and documented WinOMS v9.x (Sybase) to v10.x (MSSQL) migrations and updates.</duty>
      </duties>
    </job>
  </experience>

  <education>
    <degree>Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering</degree>
    <year>2017-2021</year>
  </education>

<reviews>
  <review id="mid2023">Mid-Year 2023 :
  Homed was not with the company for the first half of the year, but I would like to take the opportunity to share the team goals and how we performed in the first half of the year:
  Resolution time of 5 hours and escalation call closure rate within the same week 90% are team goals. At the end of Q2, the Team's resolution time was 80.64 hours and escalation closure rate was 79.1%.
  Everyone on the team is responsible for ensuring our customers' issues are resolved in a timely manner.
  Homed recently completed training for script toolkit. He should make every effort to build on his knowledge of scripts by practicing during downtimes.  He should also Install and familiarize himself with WinOMS v10.
  In the limited time working with Homed, he seems to be a fast learner, he is proactive in trying to acquire knowledge and has shown that he has good troubleshooting skills and can follow instructions given. Homed shows lots of promise with the team.
  </review>
  <review id="end2023">End-Year 2023 : 2 - 2-Exceeds
  Homed started with us halfway through the year and has hit the ground running.
  He has learned the software incredibly quickly and has made steady progress at integrating into the team.
  He regularly has some of the best performance numbers in regards to his adherence, and call evaluation scores.
  he has taken on learning the CS_toolkit early and also helps with running v10 updates for our customers.
  He has quickly become a valuable member of the team.
  Homed once again has adjusted to the WinOMS team very quickly.
  He exceeds in his performance metrics and is quick to take on new tasks that are assigned to him.
  He is also flexible and willing to work on new projects when asked.
  </review>
  <review id="mid2024">Mid-Year 2024 : 
  Homed has done a fantastic job of integrating into the team. As a newer agent, he has hit the ground running and has been learning very quickly.
  He has taken on a strong role at the forefront of many of our version 10 updates and migrations and has contributed knowledge articles to assist with them.
  He is a very valuable asset to the team with high levels of consistency.
  As of Q2, his answer percentage is 89%(3rd highest in the team), his resolution time is 22.73, he has 197 call closed. His adherence was 94.63% and conformance was 98.63%(2nd highest for both metrics).
  His call evaluation score was 98.73%(highest in the team).
  As stated before, Homed is doing a fantastic job and is a very valuable member of the team.
  </review>
  <review id="end2024">End-Year 2024 : 1 - 1-Far Exceeds
  Homed has shined on the team in this last year on a number of levels.
  He has had some of the best stats on the team among several metrics despite being a part of the team that covers our winoms v10 updates which are notoriously complicated and time consuming.
  He finished the year with the average evaluation score of 97.9, his adherence average was 93.36 for the year. His answer percentage was also second on the team at 92.77%.
  This is all while taking many complicated updates and working weekends to cover updates for our DSO customers.
  He has also helped us to solidify a process to migrate WinOMS v10 customers to a new server, which had been an incredibly problematic and difficult process.
  He created knowledge on the process of how to complete those migrations that have since been invaluable in assisting many of our other teammates to complete those migrations themselves.
  This has been a particular boon to the team and in my own perspective pushes him to the top of the team.
  </review>
  <review id="mid2025">Mid-Year 2025 : 
  Homed is another incredibly valuable member of the team.
  He is responsive to tasks given to him, will take on tasks that will often run past the end of his shift and is very flexible and can often find new solutions to existing issues.
  He has helped us to develop our v10 migration steps and documentation and has recently done the same for updating several sybase databases to v10 and continues to work on finding ways for us to migrate them together.
  He has very strong performance numbers besides. His answer percentage was 96% as of Q2, he has closed the most calls as of Q2 at 215 calls, he also has the second highest call evaluation score average for the team of 98.73.
  Homed has been and continues to be an incredible asset to the team.
  </review>
</reviews>


</resume>

